---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&difficulty=easy
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:05:13 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=b4bbdd7a08ab310fbbc7fa9a938e3205; path=/
      Upgrade:
      - h2
      Connection:
      - Upgrade
      Vary:
      - User-Agent
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which
        Greek letter represents the &quot;Half-Life&quot; logo?","correct_answer":"Lambda","incorrect_answers":["Omega","Alpha","Sigma"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which
        of these is NOT an Australian state or territory?","correct_answer":"Alberta","incorrect_answers":["New
        South Wales","Victoria","Queensland"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Board Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How
        many dots are on a single die?","correct_answer":"21","incorrect_answers":["24","15","18"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"All
        of the following are classified as Finno-Ugric languages EXCEPT:","correct_answer":"Samoyedic","incorrect_answers":["Hungarian","Finnish","Estonian"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Comics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The &quot;Pepe&quot;
        meme originated from a comic drawn by Matt Furie called &quot;Boy&#039;s Club&quot;?","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In 2006, which band
        released their debut album &quot;A Fever You Can&#039;t Sweat Out&quot;?","correct_answer":"Panic!
        At the Disco","incorrect_answers":["Twenty One Pilots","My Chemical Romance","Fall
        Out Boy"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who
        is the lead singer of Green Day?","correct_answer":"Billie Joe Armstrong","incorrect_answers":["Mike
        Dirnt","Sean Hughes","Tr&eacute; Cool"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese
        Anime & Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;To
        Love-Ru&quot;, Ren and Run are from what planet?","correct_answer":"Memorze","incorrect_answers":["Deviluke","Mistletoe","Okiwana"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which candy is
        NOT made by Mars?","correct_answer":"Almond Joy","incorrect_answers":["M&amp;M&#039;s","Twix","Snickers"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"If you are caught
        &quot;Goldbricking&quot;, what are you doing wrong?","correct_answer":"Slacking","incorrect_answers":["Smoking","Stealing","Cheating"]}]}'
  recorded_at: Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:05:13 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
